CURRICULUM VITAE

NAME: ABAHO ISRAEL **D.O.B**: 3rd May 1996

GENDER: Male
NATIONALITY: Ugandan
PLACE OF BIRTH: Ntungamo

MOBILE: +256705886700 / +256786872611

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/isra-tech
EMAIL: israelabaho@gmail.com



Summary

Creative IT technician with great expertise in Software Development. With one year working experience as a web developer.

Solid understanding of system deployment and hosting.

Great attention to detail and a talent in web design and upgrading. Enthusiastic team player who is committed to delivering top results on time within the budget and an open mind to learn more skills for my career.

Passion for keeping supervisors and clients satisfied with each project.

Work Experience

Web Developer – Orli Construction Company December 2020 – September 2021

- Developed the Orli Construction Company website from scratch and these increased online clients quote request by 17%
- Detected errors in software that decreases the loading and browsing performance by 23%
- Modified HTML, JavaScript and CSS web pages to resolve the problem in a 1-man team

- Managed to improve software's performance by 12% which resulted in 500+ leads in 2020
- Responsible for web hosting and site management, bug fixing and system upgrading.

IT Manager at ABA LIMITED (Tech Company) – Entebbe. (Part Timer) September 2018 – July 2019

- Managing all computer related activities like software installations, type and
 print activities in the organization and creating art such as logos, banners, cards,
 stickers, animations, video adverts posters etc. online of work, corporate
 personality, and client preferences.
 - Arranged photographs, illustrations, and other design pieces to convey a specific look for a company website.

PERSONAL RECENT PROJECTS (Software Development)

• Online food Store

This is an online restaurant that sells food online based on client order and delivery request. It shows detailed Information about the restaurant and a client can order food from the online shop.

Visit live demo: https://abahorestaurant.netlify.app/

Technology Used – HTML SCSS & JavaScript.

• Appointment Schedule App

This is the app I thought could help most manager CEOs or anybody to schedule meetings in a more modern way.

Visit Live demo: https://appointmentscheduleapp.netlify.app/

Technology Used – HTML SCSS & JavaScript.

• Orli Construction Company Website

This a client-based website for a construction company in my local area, it's a real life and one way to help the company reach its customers online.

Visit live demo: https://orliconstructionisra.netlify.app/

Technology Used – HTML SCSS & JavaScript

Education Background

Bachelor of Information Technology. 2017-2020

Nkumba University Main Campus.

UACE CERTIFICATE 2015-2017

Muntuyera High School – Kitunga.

UCE CERTIFICATE 2011-2014

Ntungamo High School.

PLE CERTIFICATE 2010

Mother Care Primary School.

Hobbies and Interests

- I have a strong interest in software development and introduction to more technology.
- I have strong interests in Travelling to new places meeting with people of different culture have a taste of their food.
- I have a strong interest in visual arts beyond graphic design.
- Additionally, I am also a football player, Music, and Video games are among my hobbies.

REFERENCE

Managing Director – Orli Construction Company

Email: brunokkato@gmail.com

Contact: +256705746903

Managing Director – ABA LIMITED

Email: abagrapicx@gmail.com

Contact: +256775577623

I hereby declare the above information is true and correct.

ABAHO ISRAEL.



Nkumba University

OFFICE OF THE ACADEMIC REGISTRAR

Entebbe Expressway | PO Box 237, Entebbe, Uganda | Tel: +256 (0)41 4320 283 | Fax: +256 (0)41 4320 283/4321 448 | E-mail: ar@nkumbauniversity.ac.ug | Website: www.nkumbauniversity.ac.ug

GRANTED A CHARTER BY THE GOVERNMENT OF UGANDA IN 2006

ACADEMIC TRANSCRIPT

Name:

ABAHO ISRAEL

Index No.:

2017/AUG/BIT/B222013

Gender: Date of Birth: 03/05/1998

MALE

Programme: School:

BIT SBA

Nationality: UGANDAN

AUG 2017

	Intake	:	AUG 2017	1	7822220	113
Unit of the	First	Year:	2017/2018		Pina	
			SECOND SEMESTER			
CU	Grade	GP	Course Name	CU	Grade	GF
3	В	4.0	Data Communications and Networks	4	B+	4.5
4	C+	3.5	Structured Systems Analysis and Design	4	В	4.0
4	C	3.0	Computer Mathematics	4	В	4.0
4	В	4.0	Fundamentals of Structured Programming	4	B+	4.5
4	С	3.0	Computer Repair and Maintenance	4	С	3.0
4	Α	5.0	Organization Theory	4	D+	2.5
	GPA	3 75	CCPA:3.75		CPA	3.75
	_	-			GIA	3.75
CU	Grade	GP	Course Name	CU	Grade	GP
4	С	3.0	Event Driven Programming	4	Α	5.0
4	А	5.0	ICT Strategic Management	4	B+	4.5
4	В	4.0	IT Research Design and Implementation	4	C+	3.5
4	В	4.0	Dynamic Web Page Technology	4	D	2.0
4	В	4.0	Software Engineering	4	C+	3.5
4	D+	2.5	Computer Literacy	4	В	4.0
	GPA	3.75	CGPA:3 75		GPA	3.75
	Third	Year		NEW		
cu	Grade	GP	Course Name	CU	Grade	GP
4	D+	2.5	Internet and Webpage Design	4	Α	5.0
4	D	2.0	ICT Entrepreneurship	4	В	4.0
3	С	3.0	Marketing in IT Sector	4	D	2.0
4	С	3.0	Computerized Accounting	4	B+	4.5
4	Α	5.0	Information Systems Security	4	В	4.0
4	C+	3.5	Final IT Project (Dissertation)	4	D+	2.5
	GPA	3.16	CGPA:3.63		GPA	3.66
	CU 4 4 4 3 4 4 4 4 4 4 4 4 4 4 4 4 4 4 4	CU Grade 3 B 4 C+ 4 C 4 B 4 C 4 A GPA Secon CU Grade 4 C 4 A 4 B 4 B 4 D+ GPA Third CU Grade 4 D+ 4 D 3 C 4 A 4 C 4 A 4 C 4 A 6 C	CU Grade GP 3 B 4.0 4 C+ 3.5 4 C 3.0 4 B 4.0 4 C 3.0 4 A 5.0 GPA 3.75 Second Yea CU Grade GP 4 C 3.0 4 B 4.0 4 D+ 2.5 Third Year: CU Grade GP 4 D+ 2.5 4 D 2.0 3 C 3.0 4 C 3.0 4 C 3.5	First Year: 2017/2018 SECOND SEMESTER CU Grade GP Course Name 3 B 4.0 Data Communications and Networks 4 C+ 3.5 Structured Systems Analysis and Design 4 C 3.0 Computer Mathematics 4 B 4.0 Fundamentals of Structured Programming 4 C 3.0 Computer Repair and Maintenance 4 A 5.0 Organization Theory CU Grade GP Course Name 4 C 3.0 Event Driven Programming 4 A 5.0 ICT Strategic Management 4 B 4.0 IT Research Design and Implementation 4 B 4.0 Software Engineering 4 D+ 2.5 Computer Literacy CU Grade GP Course Name 4 D+ 2.5 Internet and Webpage Design 4 D 2.0 ICT Entrepreneurship 3 C 3.0 Marketing in IT Sector 4 C 3.0 Computerized Accounting 4 A 5.0 Information Systems Security 4 C+ 3.5 Final IT Project (Dissertation)	SECOND SEMESTER	SECOND SEMESTER

Date of Completion: 20, Dec 2020

Date of Graduation: 13, Feb 2021

AWARD: Bachelor of Information Technology

CLASS OF AWARD: Second Class (Honours) Upper Division is see overleaf, Any alteration whatsoever makes the transcript invalid

Prof. Andrew Peters Yiga Academic Registrar

To verify document, check control code at http://www.nkumbauniversity.ac.ug/verify

Dr. Nazarious Rukar Dean, School of Business angira dministration



This is to certify that

Abaho Israel

having satisfied the requirements for the award of the degree of

Bachelor of Information Technology Second Class Honours (Upper Division)

of the graduating class of 2020
was admitted to the degree
at the congregation held at Nkumba University
on the **13th** day of **February** in the year **2021**.

Academic Registrar



Vice-Chancellor





